Narrator: 1, a
Speaker 1: What are you going to wear tonight?
Narrator: b
A: Where are you from?
B: I’m from Warsaw
Narrator: 2, a
Speaker 1: I don’t know what to do.
Narrator: b
Speaker 2: There’s no milk in the fridge!
Narrator: 3, a
Speaker 1: Hi. Nice to meet you.
Narrator: b
Speaker 1: Do you want meat or fish?
Narrator: 4, a
Speaker 1: The maximum weight for hand luggage is ten kilos.
Narrator: b
Speaker 2: I’m coming! Wait for me!
Narrator: 5, a
Speaker 1: Please write soon.
Narrator: b
Speaker 2: Is it on the left or on the right?
Narrator: 6, a
Speaker 1: There’s only one ticket left.
Narrator: b
Speaker 2: Brazil won the match five–one.
Narrator: 7, a
Speaker 1: I can’t see the board!
Narrator: b
Speaker 2: I love swimming in the sea.
Narrator: 8, a
Speaker 1: Have you ever read War and Peace?
Narrator: b
Speaker 2: It was cold, so she wore a coat.